<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/css/cdi.xsl' version='1.0'?><rss version="2.0"><channel>   <copyright>版权所有 - 中国日报(ChinaDaily)</copyright>   <title>China Daily  > China News</title><!-- ab 29035059 -->  <item>  <artid>29035059</artid>  <title><![CDATA[Former senior provincial legislator stands trial for bribery, election sabotage]]></title>  <link>http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/china/2017-04/21/content_29035059.htm</link>  <AuthorName></AuthorName><editor><![CDATA[郭凯]]></editor><liability><![CDATA[郭凯]]></liability>    <description><![CDATA[Wang Yang, a former senior legislator in Northeast China's Liaoning province, went on trial for accepting bribes and electoral fraud on Friday.]]></description>      <keyword><![CDATA[graft,corruption]]></keyword><content><![CDATA[<p>HARBIN -- Wang Yang, a former senior legislator in Northeast China's Liaoning province, went on trial for accepting bribes and electoral fraud on Friday.</p><p>Wang, former deputy head of the Standing Committee of Liaoning Provincial People's Congress, was accused of taking advantage of his position to seek benefits for others and of accepting money and valuables worth more than 62.9 million yuan ($9 million) between the end of 2006 and January 2013.</p><p>Prosecutors also accused Wang of sabotaging an election when he was running for deputy head of the standing committee of the provincial people's congress from December 2012 to January 2013, saying he had engaged in fraud by offering bribes and lobbying.</p><p>The case was tried at the Intermediate People's Court of Daqing City in Northeast China's Heilongjiang province.</p><p>Wang confessed to his crimes during the trial, according to the court. Sentence will be announced at a later date.</p>]]></content>        <pubdate>2017-04-21 21:40:12</pubdate> <category><![CDATA[National affairs]]></category><sourcename><![CDATA[Xinhua]]></sourcename><sourcelink><![CDATA[]]></sourcelink>     </item><!-- ae 29035059 --><!-- ab 29034667 -->  <item>  <artid>29034667</artid>  <title><![CDATA[Beijing to regulate thriving bike-sharing industry]]></title>  <link>http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/china/2017-04/21/content_29034667.htm</link>  <AuthorName></AuthorName><editor><![CDATA[郭凯]]></editor><liability><![CDATA[郭凯]]></liability>    <description><![CDATA[Beijing authorities are considering measures to regulate the ubiquitous shared bikes that benefited commuters but challenge urban management.]]></description>      <keyword><![CDATA[bike sharing]]></keyword><content><![CDATA[<p>BEIJING -- Beijing authorities are considering measures to regulate the ubiquitous shared bikes that benefited commuters but challenge urban management. </p><p>Beijing began to solicit pubic opinion Friday on a draft rule that will cap the number of shared bikes on the city's streets and promise orderly parking. </p><p>The bike-sharing business, which took off in big Chinese cities less than two years ago, allows riders to hire bikes for as little as one yuan (about $15) per hour via a mobile app and drop them off anywhere for the next users. </p><p>The service has helped riders evade Beijing's chronic traffic congestion and cut auto emissions, while haphazardly parked bikes have marred the city's image and blocked roads. </p><p>The draft rule requires district governments to set an upper limit for shared bikes in their respective jurisdictions. It says parking zones should be established around transportation hubs, shopping areas and office blocks. </p><p>Shared bikes must have GPS devices. The city's transport authorities are working on a technical specification. </p><p>In addition, the rule forbids children under the age of 12 from riding shared bikes and bans the idea of shared electric bikes "for a while." </p><p>Bike-sharing startups, such as Mobike, Ofo and Bluegogo, have put nearly 700,000 two-wheelers in Beijing, securing nearly 11 million users. </p><p>There were 18.9 million users of shared bicycles nationwide in 2016. The number is expected to hit 50 million by the end of 2017.</p>]]></content>        <pubdate>2017-04-21 20:39:56</pubdate> <category><![CDATA[Society]]></category><sourcename><![CDATA[Xinhua]]></sourcename><sourcelink><![CDATA[]]></sourcelink>     </item><!-- ae 28921868 --></channel> </rss>
