<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>NBA.com: News</title><link>http://www.nba.com/news</link><description>NBA.com delivers the latest news, video, and scores from around the NBA league.</description><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright (c) 2017NBA Media Ventures, LLC. All rights reserved.</copyright><managingEditor>webmaster@nba.com</managingEditor><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 09:46:17 EDT</pubDate><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 09:46:17 EDT</lastBuildDate><image><title>NBA.com</title><link>http://www.nba.com/news</link><url>http://i.cdn.turner.com/nba/nba/media/nba_rss.jpg</url><width>144</width><height>38</height></image><item><title><![CDATA[Shootaround (April 21) -- Isaiah Thomas should suit up for Game 3 tonight]]></title><link>http://www.nba.com/article/2017/04/21/morning-shootaround-april-21-2017/?rss=true</link><description>No. 1: Thomas expected to join Celtics for Game 3 -- By his own admission, Boston Celtics point guard Isaiah Thomas has dealt with the hardest week in his life. He flew home to the Seattle area after Game 2 to mourn with family over his younger sister's death in a car accident. As Game 3 of the Celtics' first-round series looms tonight (7 ET, ESPN), Thomas should be on the court come game time, writes Adam Forsberg of ESPN.com: </description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 08:08:39 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kevin Durant optimistic of playing in Golden State Warriors Game 3 at Portland Trail Blazers]]></title><link>http://www.nba.com/article/2017/04/20/kevin-durant-optimistic-playing-golden-state-warriors-game-3-portland-trail/?rss=true</link><description>OAKLAND, Calif. -- Kevin Durant said he felt ready to play in Golden State's Game 2 playoff win a day earlier yet the Warriors opted to be cautious with their superstar as he nurses a strained left calf.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 23:44:43 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fans rally behind Memphis Grizzlies and coach after ref rant]]></title><link>http://www.nba.com/article/2017/04/20/fans-rally-behind-memphis-grizzlies-and-coach-after-ref-rant/?rss=true</link><description>MEMPHIS, Tenn. --  Grizzlies coach David Fizdale provided Memphis fans a couple of new catchphrases from his ref rant after Game 2.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 23:34:33 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OKC Thunder needs Victor Oladipo to break out of slump]]></title><link>http://www.nba.com/article/2017/04/20/okc-thunder-needs-victor-oladipo-break-out-slump/?rss=true</link><description>OKLAHOMA CITY -- Victor Oladipo knows the Oklahoma City Thunder need more offense from him, and Russell Westbrook's wingman is feeling the heat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 22:27:26 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Utah Jazz need a big Derrick Favors vs. LA Clippers' duo of DeAndre Jordan and Blake Griffin]]></title><link>http://www.nba.com/article/2017/04/20/utah-jazz-need-big-derrick-favors-vs-la-clippers-duo-deandre-jordan-and-blake/?rss=true</link><description>SALT LAKE CITY --  With no Rudy Gobert, the Utah Jazz are hoping it's Derrick Favors time.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 21:52:44 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Milwaukee Bucks introduce Toronto Raptors to "Barney" theme song]]></title><link>http://www.nba.com/article/2017/04/20/bucks-introduce-raptors-barney-theme/?rss=true</link><description>With a split in Toronto, the Bucks have given themselves a chance to win their first playoff series since 2001. </description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 21:37:51 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cleveland Cavaliers star LeBron James reaches latest postseason milestones]]></title><link>http://www.nba.com/article/2017/04/20/lebron-climbs-postseason-scoring-rebound-lists/?rss=true</link><description>It was an epic night for Cavaliers star LeBron James in many more ways than one. </description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 23:24:01 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Utah Jazz center Rudy Gobert out for Game 3 with left knee injury]]></title><link>http://www.nba.com/article/2017/04/20/rudy-gobert-utah-jazz-out-game-3-la-clippers/?rss=true</link><description>SALT LAKE CITY (AP) -- Utah Jazz center Rudy Gobert will not play in Game 3 against the Los Angeles Clippers after hyperextending his left knee and suffering a bone contusion in the series opener.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 16:29:42 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shootaround (April 20) -- Memphis Grizzlies, fans fired up for looming Game 3]]></title><link>http://www.nba.com/article/2017/04/20/morning-shootaround-april-20-2017/?rss=true</link><description>No. 1: Fizdale's helping Memphis get fired up for Game 3 -- Memphis Grizzlies coach David Fizdale was issued a $30,000 fine by the NBA for his postgame rant about officials after Game 2. Memphis' players stepped up to pay that fine, but the words he used have set the stage for a wild Game 3 tonight, writes Geoff Calkins of The Commercial Appeal:</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 09:08:04 EDT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Golden State Warriors' Kevin Durant sits out Game 2 against Portland Trail Blazers]]></title><link>http://www.nba.com/article/2017/04/19/kevin-durant-will-sit-out-game-two-golden-state-warriors-against-portland-trail/?rss=true</link><description>OAKLAND – The Golden State Warriors did not risk Kevin Durant getting a worse injury than the strained calf muscle that sidelined him for Game 2 of their playoff series against Portland.</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 02:14:26 EDT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
